trinidadjob.com 2014-05-01

# TrinidadJob.com - Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how TrinidadJob.com Recruitment Services Limited via www.trinidadjob.com uses and protects any information that you give TrinidadJob.com Recruitment Services Limited via www.trinidadjob.com when you use this website.

TrinidadJob.com Recruitment Services Limited via www.trinidadjob.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

TrinidadJob.com Recruitment Services Limited via www.trinidadjob.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 1st August 2011.

**What we collect**

We may collect the following information:

  * name, job title, resume information
  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

**What we do with the information we gather**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**What information do we collect?**  

We collect information from you when you register on our site, fill out a form or apply for a job. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or resume information, CV. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**  

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

; To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

; To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

; To process transactions

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

; To send periodic emails

The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

**How do we protect your information?**  

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

After a transaction or application, your private information will be kept on file for more than 60 days in order to keep you updated.
